He probably won't be coming back.
Who am I?
You're nothing but my dog.
But next time, I will kill you.
This chocolate is hard to come by.
I wouldn't give it to just anyone.
Yeah.
He hated me anyway.
Come up. Hurry.
I promised you.
I'm back.
Shen Tianbai.
Come up!
[Eclipse in the Lost City]
[Episode 12]
[A few days later]
Don't move.
Ow, ow, ow, it hurts so much.
-Uncle Zhong.
-All done.
Young Master.
Look at you.
Anyone who knew you went
to Jiangcheng knew where you'd been.
Anyone who didn't know would think
you'd gone to the underworld.
What happened to you?
You went out once
and came back looking like this.
You are the only hope
of our Qingtian Gang.
The old chief made it
very clear when he was alive.
Uncle Zhong, I was wrong.
I was wrong.
Okay.
It's good that you know you were wrong.
But
are the matters in Jiangcheng
all taken care of?
Young Master, rest assured.
The fact that you saved him
hasn't leaked out at all.
Our people went to Jiangcheng by water.
The Shisha Gang won't find out.
However,
he failed to complete the mission.
How would he explain it to Xu Qingdao?
How else can he explain it?
Take the beating and take his punishment.
It's good enough for him
to come back alive.
Tianbai.
What are you doing?
I failed to complete the mission.
Please punish me.
Get up.
Sit down.
Alright.
I know everything about
what happened in Jiangcheng.
Sit.
Yes.
Who could've seen this coming?
We can't afford to get involved
in Jiangcheng's affairs from Ningcheng.
But
they can't touch anyone
I choose to protect.
Thank you, Chief.
You almost lost your lives in Jiangcheng.
How did Lu Ye come back?
I don't know, either.
We got separated after the accident.
I see.
Chief,
I'll find a chance to kill him.
You can't force the right moment.
But hearing you say that
puts my mind at ease.
I barely managed to get
through the Jiangcheng mess.
But Xu Qingdao still isn't convinced.
I must not let him get anything on me.
Looks like I'll have to be
more careful from now on.
Tianbai,
how are you feeling?
Much better. Thank you, Hui.
Damn it.
We're buddies. No need to thank me.
Remember, with me backing you,
Lu Ye is nothing.
Get some good rest.
I'm leaving.
Hui,
are you really going to deal with Lu Ye?
He dared to hit me
and mess with my buddy.
Death would be letting him off easy.
Should we tell Tianbai
and ask him to lend a hand?
I'm warning you.
Don't talk too much.
If you disturb his recovery,
I won't spare you.
Yes.
When the time comes,
I'll give Lu Ye's head directly to him.
He'll definitely like it.
That's a smart move, Hui.
Once Lu Ye sets foot in Dashijie,
we'll use this incense to knock him out.
I heard this stuff works really well.
Lu Ye,
didn't you want to return the favor?
I'll grant you your wish.
But Hui,
what if Lu Ye doesn't come?
He will definitely come.
[Do you want to know why Lu Wenbiao
was trafficking drugs?]
[Tonight at 8:00 PM. Butterfly Hall,
Dashijie. Come alone.]
Zhuque's earring?
Could it be the person
who contacted Zhuque before?
Someone in the Shisha Gang
must know something.
Even if it's a trap, I still have to go.
Young Master, what's wrong?
Nothing.
You're
still risking your life like this.
You brat,
remember, you are human,
not made of steel.
Understood, Master.
By the way,
I've recorded all the symptoms.
This poison is very strange.
Although it drives people crazy,
it also has unexpected effects.
What effects?
The closer I get
to the poison taking effect,
the sharper my senses become.
I get stronger, too,
and even my wounds heal faster.
But the stronger these effects become,
the less control I have over myself.
As expected,
it matches the report.
This is what you brought back before.
This came from the victims' bodies.
Look,
they are different.
You suspect...
I suspect there's more
than one generation of this drug.
Those people were injected
with an inferior version.
Look at their identities.
They were either beggars,
dockworkers,
or people with no legal identity.
Look at the next page.
And their bodies look
as if they'd been torn apart by wild dogs.
The way they were killed
was crude and brutal.
From what you've described,
their senses were probably heightened
all at once,
but they couldn't control it.
By the way, Master,
there is one thing that's very strange.
The maintenance dose
has to be injected every two weeks.
I noticed that the last dose was No. 1,
and this time it's No. 2.
No. 2 is darker.
The Shisha Gang's traitor
was injected with No. 2,
but he died halfway through the injection.
So you suspect it's more
than just an antidote?
Okay.
I'll take it back and run some tests.
Master,
be careful at the station, too.
The chief is too scared to take any risks.
Whenever there's trouble,
he just makes you take the fall.
You brat. Look at you, all grown up.
Now you know how
to worry about your master.
By the way,
be careful in the Shisha Gang yourself.
Don't fall into a trap.
This stuff is called Night Fog.
It's a sedative incense
imported from the West.
Customs seized a shipment recently.
I've checked the records.
Someone in the Shisha Gang
bought a large amount of it.
They've got it hidden in Dashijie.
Who?
His name is...
Hui.
Master, I'll get going.
Tianbai.
You, Lu.
You're finally in my hands.
That's for messing with my buddy.
Damn it.
Young Master.
Get him packed up
and send him back.
Yes.
Good thing you were cautious
when you came.
What's...
What's wrong with you?
Someone tried to help me.
Young Master.
I found out who did it.
Who did it?
It was a kid.
What?
The kid's always been
into this kind of thing.
He never misses.
He was the one who shot the marble.
But someone told him to do it tonight.
Who?
The kid didn't see his face clearly.
He gave the kid a piece of chocolate.
Right.
He was also wearing a very unusual watch.
The watch face was cracked.
Damn, it's all banged up.
Trust me, I'll be back before dawn.
Shen Tianbai,
could it really have been you?